

Sushil Shakya

Date of birth: 08/02/1988 | Nationality: Indian | Gender: Male |

(+91) 9821669004 | sushilshakya75@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sushil-shakya-513768191/

Skype: live:cac3cd30152f1fbe_1

1-C, STREET NO - 6, PRESS ENCLAVE, VIKAS NAGAR, UTTAM NAGAR, 110059, New Delhi, India

About me: Over the experience of 11 years, I have built a successful career in Operations and Sales & Marketing with the key proficiencies that can make a positive contribution and focusing on operational management and process improvements.

WORK EXPERIENCE

21/04/2022 - CURRENT - Gurugram, India

ASSISTANT MANAGER - SALES & OPERATIONS - DELHI ROCKS - A HOUSE OF LUXURY MARBLES

- · Handle showroom inventory in excel & sales of imported marbles and granite's.
- · Must be able to also I can make Measurement sheets, Invoices and Performa invoice.
- Use promotional techniques and prepare promotional materials to sell inventory items.
- Manage digital marketing and promotion;
 - Web Design, SEO, SMO, SMS Marketing,

Promotional activity - Brochure, Greetings, Pamphlets etc.

25/10/2018 - 16/04/2022 - Gurugram, India

ASSISTANT MANAGER - SALES & MARKETING - JINDAL ITALIA MARMO I INC.

- · Handle Hard core marketing and client schedule for visits.
- · Coordinate and handle individually meetings with Architects, Interior Designers and Builders.
- · Handle showroom sales of imported marbles and granites.
- Must be able to also I can make Measurement sheets, Invoices and Performa invoice.
- · Use promotional techniques and prepare promotional materials to sell inventory items.
- · Manage digital marketing and promotion;
 - Web Design, SEO, SMO, SMS Marketing,

Promotional activity - Brochure, Greetings, Pamphlets etc.

14/06/2014 - 30/09/2018 - New Delhi, India

ASSISTANT MANAGER - OPERATIONS - CNS WEB TECHNOLOGIES PVT. LTD.

- · Must be able to also Handle Order fulfillment for e-commerce operations.
- Managing Orders from all ecommerce platforms and ensuring all orders are prepared in time.
- Managing relationship with vendors/partners and handling problem resolution.
- · Manage all aspects of marketing operations, including key personnel.
- Attending all the complaints. Entire Process of Sales order Management Backend Operations
- Update online products & combos in ecommerce websites with handle all changes in sites.
- · Maintaining up to date files of all invoices.

24/11/2010 - 11/06/2014 - New Delhi, India

MIS EXECUTIVE - OPERATIONS - BRINKS GLOBAL INDIA

- Generating M.I.S. and analyzing business statistics and improving business.
- Assessment of cash requirement for the ATMs of different bank.
- Attending daily correspondence of the branch relating to ATM operations.
- · Collects data for all the ATMs & report to their respective banks.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

04/05/2013 - 14/09/2015 - Meghalaya, India

MBA - SALES & MARKETING - Mahatma Gandhi University

http://www.mgu.edu.in/

03/05/2008 - 06/06/2011 - Sikkim, India

GRADUATE - **ENGLISH HONORS** – University of Sikkim - Eastern Institute for Integrated Learning in Management

https://www.eiilmuniversity.co.in/

06/04/2006 - 24/05/2007 - New Delhi, India

HIGHER SECONDARY - CBSE Board Examination

http://web.delhi.gov.in/wps/wcm/connect/DOIT Education/education/home

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): HINDI

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B2	C1	B2	C1	В2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Microsoft Word | Microsoft Excel | Outlook | Microsoft Powerpoint | Social Media | Instagram | Facebook | Microsoft Office | Skype | Google Drive | Google Docs | LinkedIn | Internet user | Written and Verbal skills | Zoom | Twitter | Presenting | Team-work oriented | Good listener and communicator | Gmail | WhatsApp | Responsibility | Decision-making | Reliability | Motivated | Computer software